zankyou.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy

Through our Privacy Policy, Zankyou Ventures S.L. (“Zankyou”) informs its users of the type of data collected, the use that will be made of this data and the user’s right of access, modification or elimination of said data.

Zankyou declares that it complies with the current regulations of Personal Data Protection.

### Data controller

Zankyou certifies that the company Zankyou Ventures SL is responsible for the control of the data and is available to users through the email address help@zankyou.com, as well as via postal address: Calle Faraday, nº 7, 28049 Madrid (Spain), to discuss any queries. 

### Personal Data we gather

As part of the service provided, Zankyou requires the personal data of its users. Zankyou agrees to only collect the necessary data for the provision of its services and guarantees the use of all necessary means to protect said data. The mandatory data will be marked with an asterisk (*) in the corresponding forms. The rest of the non-mandatory data requested will be facilitated by the user under their responsibility and consent.

The data can be collected through Zankyou’s registration forms, email, chat, phone, websites associated to social networks or fairs and/or events organized by Zankyou or third parties. In the case that the data is collected through a third party, the good use and correct application of Privacy Policy is the responsibility of said third party.

The refusal to provide the data requested may result in the inability to use some parts or all of the services provided by Zankyou.

The type of data collected may vary according to the type of user:

**Couples and Guests**

For individuals or users that are couples or guests, the following data may be collected according to the services they have subscribed to and/or used:

  * Name and Surname.
  * Nationaly, gender, date and place of birth.
  * Email, phone number, address.
  * Bank details.
  * Identification documents.
  * Username on social networks.

**Professionals**

  * Name and Surname.
  * Name of the company
  * Email, phone number, address.
  * Industry area.

### How we use personal data

The personal data collected from the users will only be used in relation to the services offered by Zankyou.

**Help with the organization of the wedding and selection of Providers**

  * Allow the quick and easy search of wedding companies for users who are organizing their weddings
  * Put professionals in contact with future newly-weds who can organize their wedding by requesting information via email or phone.
  * Help users organize their wedding with the service “Virtual Assistant”. This service is carried out through phone calls, which subsequently requests information which will be sent through Zankyou on behalf of the user, with their consent, to the supplier that the Assistant considers relevant in accordance with the user’s request and information that has been previously communicated.
  * Promote products and services of the professional users through the publication of a professional tab. Through the said professional profile, all the relevant and pertinent information will be shared with couples by Province and business sector.
  * Provide the users with high quality content in order to help them organize their wedding through editorial and advertising articles.
  * Allow the users to be involved in the Zankyou community through the publication of public comments both in magazine articles and the files in the Directory.
  * During the period of time Zankyou is connected to its users or until the user withdraws consent, Zankyou reserves the right to send electronic communication related to the services offered by Zankyou or its associates and communications of general content related to wedding planning.

**Gift Registry**

  * The data collected from the Beneficiaries through the Gift List Service will be collected in compliance with the spanish law “Ley 10/2010, de 28 de abril” which defines in particular the elements of information related to knowing your client. Personal data and other information collected as a part of activating a Gift List will be used to identify the identity of the beneficiaries.
  * The bank data provided as part of activating the Gift List will only be used to transfer the contributions received by the Beneficiaries from the Contributors into the associated bank account.
  * The personal data collected of the guests during the contribution process will not be used by Zankyou, with the exception of necessary communication related or derived from the same process. 

### Sharing Information

Zankyou undertakes to implement all the necessary means in order to protect the user’s data and communicate this information only within the framework of legislation that governs its activity or in one of the cases explained below.

Users that could be defined as couples accept the distribution of their data to companies that appear on Zankyou and in ones the user has shown interest in, especially during first contact made through the Zankyou portal or during the participation in a competition organized jointly by Zankyou and one of its associates.

Zankyou agrees to hide the personal data of a user who deleted hisprofile from providers who they were previously in contact with through Zankyou, however will not be responsible if this data was previously collected by the Provider and the use of said data. In this case, the responsibility will be of the said provider.

In the case that the user has subscribed to or used Zankyou’s Gift List service, the personal data provided by the user with relation to the use of this service may be communicated to payment institutions, public organizations related to this service, competent authorities or potential associates of Zankyou in the case that the user has opted for a Gift List proposed by both Zankyou and one of its associates.

Professional user’s data will be communicated to third parties only in the context of connecting future service providers and couples or according to the legislation that governs Zankyou’s activity as mentioned above.

### Transfer to other countries

Zankyou is an international company based in Spain. For this reason, Zankyou informs its users that their data could be used on an international level. This would only occur when necessary and Zankyou would put in place all of the necessary security measures to protect said data.

### Conservation Period

The collected data will be retained during the user’s use of Zankyou’s services or until the user exercises their right to cancel their account.

After the deletion of the users account, Zankyou will only retain the necessary data as a part of their legal and/or contractual obligations. Once this conservation period has passed, the data will be eliminated completely and definitely.

### User’s Rights

The user can exercise their rights of access, rectification, deletion, portability, limitation and/or opposition to treatment.

The execution of these rights can be carried out directly from the user’s profile, they can also in the case of doubt or technical concern get in contact with Zankyou through their postal address Calle Faraday, 7 - 28049 Madrid (Spain), by email at help@ zankyou.com or via phone at (646) 564-5601.

In the case that the user believes there has been a violation of their rights; they can send a complaint directly to Zankyou through the contact information previously stated or the Spanish Protection of Data Agency: <https://www.agpd.es/>.

### Security

Zankyou informs its users that all the necessary means have been implemented, from a technological as well as organizational point of view, to guarantee the security of personal data and avoid loss, alteration or unauthorized processing.

### Children

The use of personal data of minors will be entirely the responsibility of the user who confirms they have the right to share this information and will not publish it in any circumstance which may harm a minor.

Zankyou provides its users with the email help@zankyou.com and the phone number (646) 564-5601.
